500 years ago area the western region spreads a fable
They said comes from the earth buddhist priest…
Can lead his three apprentices to go to one to call Shache the city the place
Took one batch already to check the very many centuries ancient times religious texts
In the fable only then this buddhist priest may translate these religious texts
When the time comes the common people can by the religious texts influence
Lays down the butcher knife no longer to kill one another
But goes to one with this buddhist priest to call the western heaven of heavens the place
There person peaceful coexistence forever all cannot have the war
The tang dynasty pilgrim monk learned from experienced people
The tang dynasty pilgrim monk came
Too good their priests and disciples several finally arrived our Shache city
Cannot
Sings dances is his line of business
The big fellow apprentices you stare at the pillar to look at any
Once some people said to me
If does not want to tell the secret others to look a Dongkou to say
Said later will live it with the balling up
I want to say originally listens for this Dongkou
Who knew has not opened the mouth…On has been nipped by the centipede
Others all arrive on the mountain to look for the dashu to say
Where some people did say to the pillar
But you look like such disconsolately are not likely for the strip centipede
Does not know but to me for any
Has the monster
Your head constipation
The big fellow apprentices have the fierce look
As soon as if had the monster to enter a city he to see
Made sense the men and women all to come out
Not any improper
These beautiful women have not hidden
The old person and the child also all come out dance
Child
A our early morning all has not seen the child
Extinguished
If tang dynasty pilgrim monk tomorrow sunrise before…
We do not give you the dashu fine to receive in exchange our child
They take us the child to feed the millennium insect monster
Now the natural lifespan you the priests and disciples had bad luck
Yes…
Bold
Master worker
Dares to harm my master worker
Wukong
Was the master worker called you not to want to have a fit of temper you to forget
Let the master worker exit by the German clothing monster to be right
Womanishly fussily whispers day in day out Luo Luo Suosuo
Now the human five people six play the role of the god
Does not want the smelly master worker
Becoming aware energy
I knew you have prejudice only me to the master worker now to be full of confidence
Looked how I do exit to influence them
Each…Shache city friend…
Why bother are you are sir
If you the hand shakes do not have to study others to chop the human
This knife flings flings does not fling center very ugly
Is right
Chops my master worker to look at the palm
Must hits is all right hits me to do
So long as has eaten the tang dynasty pilgrim monk meat we on the immortality
Is the eternal overlord
I come
You…Thinking…Does…
We 4466 do decide
Careful
I spoke incorrectly any
Wants to play ? the standard with my Lao Sun not to be absurd
The Wukong your wool dyes had been inferior to tries my wool
My had almost forgotten was called the disciples and followers already not to need to pluck hairs again
Italy lives by the heart is the kingly way
I change
Wukong
Wukong you how fellow apprentices
You how
Master worker…Taking care
Pig treasure
The master worker knew you cleverest also most do not give up you
The pig is valuable your stupid time to abdicate…
The feelings good are useless exit only to be able bring death…
You look down upon my me to go…
You die coming back which decides
Wukong…
Spatial…Empties your
Listens to this root to decide the sea god needle to be able to deliver you to walk
The master worker cannot walk the master worker said has had by the German clothing monster
Is right
You come me most to dislike others “”
I call you “” 88
You also “” not “” “” not “”
I do not dare…
“” Not “”
Do not think takes the cotton candy to come to me to eat me not to cry
This is not the cotton candy is the Jin'gang silk
Today my Lao Sun ???? you to have rolls far far
The Wukong again do not do intentionally the sinister aspect
Because you could not deceive the master worker to let loose me
Listens if you want the Jin'gang stick to listen to your…
Said “loves your for 10,000 years”
If you want it to stop saying “I do not love you”
Wukong…Wukong…Puts down the Wukong me
Listens to master worker's speech to put down me
Walks
Master worker
Humph these for half year heaven did not know has sent any insanely
Is not falls a stone to fall a strange egg to get down
Tonight also falls a fool
Is not the fool is infatuated is sentiment huge saint Sun Wukong
How did you know
You had not seen on his body is inserting the root Jin'gang stick
But has not thought of this monkey such soft and fair skin
Is he 500 years ago and purple light fairy maidens love that…
Sentiment saint
Do not send the wave
The sentiment saint is simply the joke…
You understood the fart woman most to be in a stew are this kind of man
If ascends the sky gives me again an opportunity
I can say three characters to this girl
I love you
If must certainly add a deadline in this section of sentiment I to hope is…
10,000 years 10,000 years…
Shutting up
Sun Wukong in here tang dynasty pilgrim monk certainly in neighbor
Clumsy duckweed
I…I came
Is Luo Ping…
Any
Is the Luo duckweed is not the clumsy duckweed
How aren't you clumsy can the daughter fresh such clumsy
Asks his daughter to look at him
You call that any any to look at him
Gave her the daughter to be most appropriate
All female saw ?? has been able to flow Kazak Lhatse
Only then his daughter could not eat definitely by ??
?? also ? to does not have the appetite
Ask…
You awake such quickly
Knows me attractively therefore awakes ahead of time
Mmm any
You use that the sexy sound to want to soak me
Do not think I attractively good bully
The most poisonous beautiful will of the people do you have have listened
Do not think you are the sentiment saint I can have a liking for you
I became famous iced cold
Never a man me
Is not you listens to me to say mountain beautiful young lady…
How can you know my name
Although I ???? in the monster
But you do pay attention to my you do not plan likes me
You had a liking for me to hang
Even if adds for 100,000 years also equally to hang
You…The thing has fallen…
Falls from your body
Does not have to speak
My any had not said
Knew you can say like this
Do not think you may confuse me not in a moment
You evil do not coexist with me
My spookiness imposing healthy tendency does not invade
Then you can let loose me
Certainly is not good
Perhaps you can drool my beauty to encroach upon me
I thought this kind of probability really is small also is small…
Has been guessed very ashamed by me
I thought you read some books also to have a conscience
Good I use my chastity to come with you to be abundant
Feeding…
These are the Jin'gang silk
Certainly must use woman's saliva only then to be able to dissolve
Bold
Eats my bean curd I not to be able to fear
In our evil faction the human cannot ????
Had said certainly can do
Bold
You do study me to speak the sexy appearance
Is unfair to me not to have your that sex appeal…
Mountain beautiful young lady
Which part can't I divide your am am beautiful which part am colorful
You…
Calculated on your cow almost your working as
No wonder they said your honest center person extremely is all sly
Really not wrong
Do not disguise to be mad again I did not have to a your feeling
If I were angry not represent me to have to you feel
Not only therefore I am not angry I also to want * to open your you to nip me
Delicious
Can I quite thirsty give me to select the water to drink
Certainly may
In our evil faction the human is not the unprincipled person does wants to maltreat you
Thanking
You do any
Must not such have politeness to entice me
You thought I did not know
After you have wanted the water compels me to feed you to drink
I hold the time which you get up you depend on
How then I do manage
I shove open you am not
How can it be that didn't shove open you is not I does not owe is big
So long as you give me the water to drink me to comply oneself to drink
Why do I want to believe you…
You won I to say only you
Your does this have how only then to give me the water to drink
Does not have to ask
Did not ask has Shui He
Does not have to ask in reply
Buddha also can grasp crazily
Added does not want to occupy me to be cheap
Your mouth collects such nearly does any
You are want to kiss my rascal
I thought…I want the saliva to drink for do not give
For kisses one to you
Otherwise kissed has certainly had to walk I to me to kill you
Going against
Why did my finally * my apprentice always say I ?
Calculated your conscience discovered reins in at the brink of the precipice has not made…
Being unfair to…Asked you to leave said again
I go against you not to be suitable
Since you knew is wrong my gratitude and grudges to be also distinct
Good
I take the water to you you to be possible now do not plan runs
You run I to break your leg
Under very big egg who
Had not thought your semblance is such clumsy…
Inside unexpectedly that America
Praises me to be quite repugnant unexpectedly
You tease me
I tease you
You said any a moment ago
I want…Shui He
Plays with me
Why do you have like this to me
Was afraid
The fear was knows is wrong
You cannot Wugong
Then you said quickly “loves your for 10,000 years”
Your this rascal
I ask you
The flattery said…
Loves your for 10,000 years
Stopping from time to time…
I do not like you stopping…
Originally is taking the human said only then can be effective
Then you quickly said
Your this does not die the conscience
I had said likes you not being able to change in our evil faction the human…
I knew
I am not call you to me to say I call you to say to the club
That also almost…
I did not love you
Do not hit my tang dynasty pilgrim monk in here
You are the tang dynasty pilgrim monk
Holds the tang dynasty pilgrim monk
Oh any matter
Which group invincible force injuries me the human
You awake you do not die you awake…
Mother…You awake
Do not die…Mother…
I cannot die I am feign death
Your quite pleasant to hear mother said
This is divides the water drop foot ? two people to sit
Brings the tang dynasty pilgrim monk to go to nobody the place
Looked for the opportunity to give him eats
After has eaten it you could not die on the immortality
These ruffians died nobody to dare to bully you
I did not fear others bully me
I knew I clumsily harm you always to smile by the human
How meets you is most attractive
Nobody is more attractive than you
Remembered looks for the opportunity to eat the tang dynasty pilgrim monk
I walked
The mother I cannot start
I fell in love with him
Had not really thought my old trade union is a buddhist priest
I dodge
The your majesty tang dynasty pilgrim monk disappears without a trace
His three apprentices in my hand I did not believe he does not come back
This minute water drop is where makes
Such clumsy pierced at the first thrust
What didn't you ask the way on matter do not have
But this nautical mile black japan hemp Ukraine's I…
Asks the strip fish to ask the way very is also normal
Who knew he gesticulates can for puncture the bead
That is not the fish is a lobster
Knew early why didn't say us…Oh
Is evil does not coexist the means not to link up with you
Turtle prime minister is you
How can you do this appearance
You added all blames your apprentice not not well…
“Decided the sea god needle” to rob has made the entire seabed out of trim
Dragon King from spits early on East China Sea that late
Harms everybody to be compelled to have to immigrate to come ashore
That is not “decides the sea god needle”
For me…Returns to give back to me…
To…That is the Wukong Jin'gang stick
But the Wukong he has difficult now
I really hoped you can help me to rescue him
Do not tease me also to want to ask the human to help…
“Decides the sea god needle” to return to give back to me
Turtle prime minister…Isn't your such procedure resembles to right
Any procedure
Since this Jin'gang stick is a Wukong
Then I should return to give back to his then you to ask him again first
Obtains him after to agree returns to give back to you by him
Like this only then conforms with the procedure
Snatches my thing also to have to obtain him to agree
Related snatches thing this matter to belong to in legal the question
On is dissimilar with the present situation
Your mother “decides the sea god needle” to return to give back to quickly I
Closes my mother any matter she not to take how also you
Lets loose him
Again “did not decide the sea god needle” to return to give back to my I to kill you
This procedure is not right
Is not right
Natural
Now
Decides the sea god needle not in here there her…
You have any reason to have to kill me to take her
“Decides the sea god needle”
Killed my her to be able to give you not necessarily
Does not kill my her also not necessarily not to be able to give you
Therefore kills me not to be supposed to decide by you
Should decide by her
Not wrong
If I kill him am because evil does not coexist
Also I with you all am not the human
Strict said we are in the person of same belief or convictions the monster I should help you
Then you do not begin
Kills the homicide he the mother
Is kills him or kills his mother
Kills him a bit faster…
Kills his mother
Why I ???? I with his mother to have to kill his mother
I go against your lung you to kill do not kill
To you said I do not kill his mother
Moreover I did not know his mother did not know his mother does live in where
Really very difficult to look to my mother's address
I go against you not to be suitable…
Turtle prime minister…Turtle prime minister…
Tang dynasty pilgrim monk
You have killed my turtle prime minister
Not…Does not close my matter
Has killed him
Loves your for 10,000 years
How turns the ship
The mistake is a speed boat
How
Are we now are travelling for a feeling good
Why well has to travel
Just did that many monster kill me not to hit them to be how good
Well does hits the human
In your these evil factions the human cannot open the mouth to ask others for help
Only is begins to hit the human
As soon as opened the mouth your to open the mouth on to say definitely a moment ago that tortoise
He dies closes my any matter
Any does not close your matter
Your finally that speech poisonous you said your mother's address is very difficult to look
My mother always moves really very difficultly to look
South did not have idea only then has gone to the fontanel to move the reinforcement
You must surrender
My tang dynasty pilgrim monk line is standing straight ????
Fears their any not equally with your me
Suppresses me to accompany you well to go
To south the fontanel do not talk too much
Any speech all said by me
But south this we must go to the fontanel I not to recognize know the way
You lead us to be good
You left that lack prospects or a bright future
Under this died has decided…
How does this manage
Overruns
Do not go
Some people in
How can you in inside
You come out you a bit faster to come out…
Originally I in inside
You a bit faster come out
Asks you not to make here well crisp
Very big inkslab
The tang dynasty pilgrim monk you also have on the courage south the fontanel
Do not be noisy
To you said is called you not to talk too much
Four great heavenly gods
My apprentice Sun Wukong has had an accident I is prays for rescue
If I did not help you you to be able to kill me
You knew I always do not open the buddhist commandment against taking life
Why then on your body can have the blood
Is turtle prime minister…
Is turtle prime minister
Such said East China Sea Dragon King has not treated unjustly you
He refuses stubbornly to close my matter
Why can he die
Is said definitely by me…
My meaning meant…
All blames you to say was saying the present linked I all to believe
Believes any
Is you said has a clear conscience that you to do must fear them
Who doesn't have to say I fear them
Wants to hit back to me hits
Loves your for 10,000 years
The day will all dare to kill that seductively attractive girl
Mother
The growth Son of Heaven died
Also looked walks quickly
Also flies…
The tang dynasty pilgrim monk you kill unexpectedly…
Made embarrassedly you from head to foot all are the blood
I help you scratch
Bidding good-bye
Your I evil do not coexist…We bid good-bye in light of this
Bid good-bye you too not to have the conscience
I rescued your you to dismantle the bridge after crossing unexpectedly
You added
You each time said several have not hit the human the day all to kill now by you
The responsibility pushes for me is unexpectedly you begins first
I shirk any responsibility
You just the man spoke time I the half a word speech all have not said
I gave the foot you the face am your that…
“I fear your any” the that smelly fart
Others only then can think is flat you
Is you extends the foot to stumble others others only then to be able to hang
I stumble he am…
Walking
You do not love me
Has not loved
I do not believe
Looks clearly
Does not love
You said again
Does not like rolling
Walking…
Oh…Such husbands and wives head of a bed do not hit the tail block sum
You love
I am a Buddhist
I did not understand is in love
My love is uses for to universal restoration
Such said also includes me
Except you
You really that hate me
Good hates
All does not care about me
Completely not
Then you continue to be you the buddhist priest
Three characters
I like you saying
Did not say…Do you have see the Buddhist to be in love
Has sees the buddhist priest to have the girlfriend not to say
Said
Kills all didn't say
Then I
Mental illness compels others to say…
Again waits for your a while I not to believe you do not look for me
Resembled and so on to be very long
Extinguished him really to look for me
But went astray the direction
Has destroyed but if he runs looks for me blind I
How can it be that can't be very sad
My he certainly has not will be very pitiful
Makes table of vegetarian dishes to wait for him to come back to eat meal
I must certainly boil this food
I with your bar on
Good changes a thing to eat hungrily
Loves your for 10,000 years
Does any others to be a vegetarian
I can go with the Wukong suit
Our five big mass organizations have chopped this together female
Five big mass organizations
We must eat you now
Is good for a response
You like eating then eat me only then not to fear
Your this three women are lovelorn are lovelorn
Certainly was is flung by the man has lived does not have may love
Good I help you
Feeds under the knife to keep the human
Your this crowd of ruffian you the monster all was inferior to
You ate my good me are Tang three…
Tang three is you
Your mother just everywhere asked you to be called you to go back eats meal
Everybody in under tang dynasty pilgrim monk
Your real pig you are not like this let human opening meal
You…You are unexpectedly the such ugly woman domestic animal you
To wrong has not eaten me
??? really all are the younger sister masters
I only then did not believe you have that greatly
Only if you drill me from the red child pants crotch bottom only then to believe
Yes…To…
You drill looked you drill me again to bid good-bye with you
Coming
Red child this whole life he on has not traded the underpants
Then was smelly you all to dare to drill has taken you simply
Good move
You dared to drill me to kill you
How the devil do you look at others Mr. Tang to own woman
Mr. Tang I have taken you
You suppressed the tone on to do the matter decide
Actually I see you all have the compassion very much
Therefore later each other will have take to like as liking seriously melting the enemy
How Mr. does Tang the enemy hit our us to manage
? to does not hit back
We…With likes influencing him
Then he wants to kill you
Also does not revolt
With likes causing them to lay down the butcher knife
The tang dynasty pilgrim monk you kill the four great heavenly gods
I must calculate the account with you
Does not have the relations with him is I kills
? again do not maintain me
The devil you have a look others to have the multi- love
Mr. Tang this matter I very
To very…Very
Bold evil portents who dares to help him me not to be impolite to who
Looks at any Pi ?
I cannot hit your me to be able to use to like moving you
I love you
I come
Hits light one
Who comes also some to dare
Don't anxious…
We have compared to a butcher knife stronger strength are our life
Right not to Mr. Tang
I casually said you seriously
Here has the great amount…
Loves your for 10,000 years
Does not want
Calm spot
Again calm spot
Surely calm spot…
I have opened the buddhist commandment against taking life…
How can I be the Buddhist who ????
Mr. Tang… Let him peacefully
Feigned death a moment ago that two also had the invincible force
Vanishes immediately to me
Do not let the tang dynasty pilgrim monk know
The such lacking virtue move all can let that smelly young married woman want to come out
Had the Tang Xuanzang meat to eat
You left blame own again
I knew you open the buddhist commandment against taking life are for me
I knew I am not the human and so on I can vanish
If you also want to rescue Sun Wukong you to go with the monsters to chat
I thought they very much ???
You do not give up me
I believed continuously the heaven has ????, ????
But I finally saw today is…
Does not divide the right and wrong wanton slaugter to be innocent
Before your I evil do not coexist
But I already turned a murder devil now
Turned in an evil faction the human
Not wrong
We later the common onset and retreat will call the monsters…
Rescues Sun Wukong to be called him together to buy stock
Let him kill and torch degenerates together
Good
We applaud for the pledge rescue the Wukong together
How
I promise you and you rescue Sun Wukong together
But you must remember
If one day you if catches up with the speech again which I walk
I could not again give you this kind of opportunity
Saying it and mean iting
Although but I am deceive him I also am am good for him
I to these monsters said the tang dynasty pilgrim monk was poisoned
Takes for a month only then may eat him
The hope might deceive them inside this period of time
Is called them to help the tang dynasty pilgrim monk to rescue him apprentice Sun Wukong
?? difficult to make the monster to be more difficult
Makes the monster to have to have the monster the makings
First comes up shortly must let the human think…Monster
Looks at any
Can ??? bully the human
Can bully the human
Said can
Hits back I to play two move of you to experience
Do not move me to help you to scratch the medicated wine
Where do you trace my
Really is wants others the life
This kind of woman does not know the sense of honor
Under broad daylight big crowd of people
Wiggles forward like this with a strange opposite sex…
I ? to cannot like this
I can certainly the man who likes with me
Under quiet at dead of night romantic star light…
Jumps three pastes ??
Beautiful
Yesterday the eurypholis major elder sister has taught me a dance well amusing
I teach you
Not study
I speak incorrectly an any for early morning all to pay no attention to me
Hangs receives the fist I to keep off
Although this fist makes an effort very much hitting on my face
But I deep deeply feel this man's wild breath
Whenever therefore evening this ?? sleeps soundly time